Cole Bielskis

IT Technician

Dedicated Computer Science student with extensive experience in customer service. Accustomed to fast-paced demanding work with emphasis on precision and customer satisfaction. Passionate team player with an eagerness to develop skills complimentary to those of fellow coworkers.

Education

7/2018 - 12/2020

Associate of Science: Computer Science & Applications Development

College of San Mateo - San Mateo, CA

- Relevant Coursework Completed: Computer Networking, Java: Object-Oriented Program Design, Programming Methods and Data Structures, Python, NoSQL/SQL databases.
- Dean's List Fall 2019-Fall 2021
- Continuing education in Computer Science for transfer to a 4-year program.

Work History

11/2017 - 7/2020

Bartender

Per Diem, San Francisco, CA

- Edited order tickets, employee profiles and generated revenue reports using Revel
 Point of Sale system.
- Rectified complaints effectively to maintain customer satisfaction.
- Diagnosed and repaired connectivity issues in POS systems.

7/2013 - 1/2017

Lead Bartender

Il Fornaio, Burlingame, CA

- Trained new employees on Micros Point of Sale software, drink preparation techniques and equipment use protocols.
- Installed, upgraded and supported peripheral equipment such as printers,
 scanners and fax machines.
- Consulted with management to establish standards and optimize performance
- Maintained detailed inventories and notified management of liquor, wine, beer and bar equipment needs.

8/2011 - 1/2013

Head Coach Girls Water Polo

Carlmont High School, Belmont, CA

- Designed training programs to improve conditioning, technique and tactics for both junior varsity and varsity squads.
- Evaluated competition performance to analyze strategies and develop counter approaches to improve team and individual performance.

Contact

Address

San Francisco, CA,

94112

Phone

(650)483-6091

E-mail

cole.bielskis@gmail.com

Skills

Communication

PC/MAC OS Support

Software/Hardware Troubleshooting

Self-Management

Adaptability